So again we achieved a lot over the last lectures.
Son derslerden ok daha fazla baar elde ettik.
We have our orders page finished,
Siparilerimizin tamamlanm sayfas var.
We have our burger builder which is really working great, which leads us forward to the checkout page
Boulder' gerekten ok iyi alyor. Hangisi zemin tahtamz, formun burada bir akam yemei
where we load the checkout form, the form here isn't finished but we can issue an order, we are redirected
yklediimiz deme sayfasna ynlendiriyor ancak bittiinde bir sipari verebiliriz, bundan sonra yeniden
thereafter and we can see that order here,
ynlendirebiliriz ve o siparii burada grebiliriz.
so that is all working fine.
Yani hepsi iyi alyor.
Now things we can improve are that
imdi elbette iyiletirebileceiniz eyler ld.
Checkout form which I just mentioned, this one here
Buraya daha nce burada bahsettiime bir gz atn.
and of course in general the state management of our application. We can already see that we have to
Ve tabii ki genel olarak uygulamanzn devlet ynetimi, baz reddetme yntemlerini
use some tricks and workarounds from time to time, that is something we'll improve throughout this course once
kullanmamz gerektiini grebilir ve zaman zaman redkse daldmzda bir eylerin bu
we dive into redux
dersten iyileeceini grebiliriz.
though. Still we have a nicely working application which already is way more than just a tiny little
Hl ok kk ve kk bir yan projeden ok daha gzel bir
side project.
uygulama var.
Awesome work thus far,
u ana kadar harika bir alma.
let's now I'm deeper into forms and then additional features
imdi formlara ve daha sonra ek zelliklere derinlemesine bakalm.
The react ecosystem offers to us.
Yeniden hareketli ekosistem bize sunuyor.